Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/hao-nguyen-b0a8aa62 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Quality Control
Java
Quality Assurance

Languages

English

Hao Nguyen

Looking For Manual Tester.

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

A software engineer with 9+ years of experience in Web/ Software testing, in various fields (Media, E-commerce and Management System); with great foundation and experience in manual testing skills.

Having solid knowledge in testing web application, mobile application. Having practical experience in working with American and Japanese clients. Extremely good at problem solving skills, task management, time management and quick learning abilities. Friendly, open-minded and determined in completing tasks even under high pressure.

Experience

Forix

Tester

March 2019 - Present (6 years 1 month)

82 Trần Huy Liêu

Test magento and shopify ecommerce websites.

Elca Vietnam

Tester

January 2018 - February 2019 (1 year 2 months)

Dien Bien Phu - Binh Thanh.

Agile Tester - Manual Testing for java apps.

Global CyberSoft

Tester

August 2014 - January 2018 (3 years 6 months)

Quang Trung software city

Agile Tester - Manual Testing for web application and java apps.

Officience

Tester

August 2012 - August 2014 (2 years 1 month)

Page 1 of 2

Nguyen Dinh Chinh.

Agile Tester - Manual Testing for web application.

Simple Solutions Taipan Vietnam

Senior QC

April 2011 - July 2012 (1 year 4 months)

Manual Testing for web application and Applying Selenium in regression testing for web application.

Formos

Senior QC

July 2008 - March 2011 (2 years 9 months)

Manual Testing for web application and Researching Selenium.

Quantic

Quality Control

July 2007 - June 2008 (1 year)

Manual Testing for web application.

Education

HUI

Engineer's degree, Computer Science · (2004 - 2007)